Guide to the New World Writing Records
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Clippings and Foreign Reviews Files, 1952-1960; Series VI; 1.3; (3 boxes)
  - Issue #14 Clippings, 1958 (Box 53, Folder 1318)
  - Issue #15 Clippings, 1959 (Box 53, Folder 1319)
  - Issue #15 Foreign Reviews, 1960 (Box 53, Folder 1320)
  - General Clippings, 1952-1959 (Box 53, Folder 1321-1323)
  - General Foreign Reviews, 1954 (Box 53, Folder 1324)
- Oversize Material, 0.25; (1 box)
  - Issue #1 Clippings and Foreign Reviews (from Series VI), 1952 (Box 54, Folder 1325)
  - Issue #2 Clippings and Foreign Reviews (from Series VI), 1952-1953 (Box 54, Folder 1326)
  - Issue #3 Clippings and Foreign Reviews (from Series VI), 1953 (Box 54, Folder 1327)
  - Issue #4 Clippings and Foreign Reviews (from Series VI), 1953-1954 (Box 54, Folder 1328)
  - Issue #5 Clippings and Foreign Reviews (from Series VI), 1954 (Box 54, Folder 1329)
  - Issue #6 Clippings and Foreign Reviews (from Series VI), 1954 (Box 54, Folder 1330)
  - Issue #7 Clippings and Foreign Reviews (from Series VI), 1955 (Box 54, Folder 1331)
  - Issue #8 Clippings and Foreign Reviews (from Series VI), 1955 (Box 54, Folder 1332)
  - Issue #9 Clippings and Foreign Reviews (from Series VI), 1956 (Box 54, Folder 1333)
  - Issue #10 Clippings and Foreign Reviews (from Series VI), 1956-1957 (Box 54, Folder 1334)
  - Issue #11 Clippings and Foreign Reviews (from Series VI), 1957 (Box 54, Folder 1335)
  - Issue #12 Clippings and Foreign Reviews (from Series VI), 1957-1958 (Box 54, Folder 1336)
  - Issue #13 Clippings and Foreign Reviews (from Series VI), 1958 (Box 54, Folder 1337)
  - Issue #14 Clippings and Foreign Reviews (from Series VI), 1958 (Box 54, Folder 1338)
  - Issue #15 Clippings and Foreign Reviews (from Series VI), 1959 (Box 54, Folder 1339)
  - General Clippings and Foreign Reviews (from Series VI), 1952-1959 (Box 54, Folder 1340)